[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 11]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Author: Shan Gu Jun]
[Main Hall]
[Pure Land on Earth]
I didn't expect you
to believe in this.
There are things
you can't decide.
You can only pray.
When you got your fortune read,
the master talked much to you.
What did he say?
I got medium luck.
It roughly means
I can't have the best of both worlds.
I have to make a choice.
That's how things work..
You have to lose some to gain some.
Especially
with your career.
If you want to play it safe,
it's hard to make a breakthrough.
I'll take a look over there.
But I wasn't praying for my career.
[Pure Land on Earth]
I was praying for marriage.
[Main Hall]
Is it for me?
You don't want it?
Forget it then.
I want!
[Main Hall]
I'm going to visit my parents.
Would you come with me?
Happy New Year.
I won't bother you.
When you come back,
I have something to tell you.
Can't you tell me now?
Some things
are not meant for now.
[Main Hall]
Two set of incense sticks.
Still in the hospital?
I'm going shopping with Lin Zhihuan.
It's jamaican coffee.
It tastes good. Try it.
Hello, aunties.
Hello, Yu'an.
Mom.
I need to take a call.
Go ahead.
Yu'an is getting more and more handsome.
Exactly.
Among the kids of his generation,
Yu'an is the best.
Mature and poised.
Reliable.
Yes.
His career is really taking off.
Indeed.
Just small-time stuff.
His dad
doesn't want him messing with this.
But he insists.
Hello, Wen Jian. What's up?
Just wishing you a happy New Year.
What are you busy with?
Dealing with family.
Say hello to your parents for me.
Oh, right.
Yu'an is at the age to get married, right?
Is there any suitable match for him?
I'm counting on you to set him up.
Hey, you know a girl, don't you?
Oh, yes.
I happen to know one..
She's quite nice.
Really?
Her dad is in real estate.
A perfect match for your family.
I'll introduce you to her some other day.
Bring her here.
I'll have the maid prepare some dishes.
Okay.
Later,
Aunt Li is bringing her daughter over.
Have a good chat with the girl.
Mom,
I kept repeating myself.
Stop interfering in my private life.
I'm just worried about you.
Look at you,
you haven't dated in so long.
What, you want to be single forever?
I don't have the time
or the energy
to date someone I don't like.
Then tell me,
who do you like?
Who is she?
Your partner, Wen Jian?
You investigated me?
[SenZhou Rehabilitation Hospital]
[Fire safety]
[Outpatient Clinic]
[SenZhou Rehabilitation Hospital]
Well...
So what if I did?
What's wrong with that?
I just expect you
to find a girlfriend,
get married,
and give us a grandbabe soon.
Honestly,
I'm fed up with his sour face.
Auntie Cheng,
I'll tell my dad what you said,
so he can have a good talk
with Uncle Zhuo.
You brat, you're such a smooth talker.
Doesn't your mom pressure you?
Her nagging is useless.
I won't listen anyway.
But Yu'an
is more obedient than me.
Push a little harder,
and it might just work.
Shut up.
All right, enough talk.
Keep trying, Auntie.
I'm on your side.
See?
He's so good at chatting.
Then look at yourself.
What a waste of your height
and your handsome face.
Come on, go flirt
with some girls out there!
Mom,
I'll say it one more time.
Stop interfering in my private life.
I know what to do.
Hey.
I...
I haven't finished yet.
Bye, Auntie.
Brat.
Double-check the project.
It's very important to us.
Got it.
Wen Jian.
Go on.
What did you say to my mom?
Sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You visited my mom in the hospital.
Her condition finally improved,
and you just had to provoke her.
Why did she end up like this?
Don't you know?
Of course I know.
That's exactly why I had to see her.
Shu Tinglan,
what happened?
[Zhuoyuan Technology]
Wen Jian,
you...
Tinglan.
Bother my mom again,
and you'll end up just like Shu Minghai!
As for you…
I don't want to know
your choice anymore.
Shu Tinglan!
Yu'an!
The meeting is in ten minutes.
Let them wait.
Show's over!
[In Deep Mourning]
[Tribute]
It's been so many years...
For so many years,
Jian could only call him dad in secret.
Now he's gone.
For the last time,
I just want her
to call him dad properly.
Dad!
Mom?
Mom!
I've told you again and again.
Jian and her mother have it hard.
You should go easier on her.
Your mother is in a very bad state.
She often threatens to commit suicide!
Tinglan,
Shu Minghai is so cruel!
Zhuo Yu'an,
only one between Wen Jian and me.
Who do you choose?
Shu Tinglan,
what happened?
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Shu Tinglan.
Zhuo Yu'an,
just go.
I need to make sure you're really okay.
I mean,
I don't want any personal contact
between us ever again.
What do you mean?
Tinglan?
Make yourself clear.
I'm really clueless!
Shu Tinglan?
Tinglan.
What's this supposed to mean?